<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aaron&#39;s Site</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Aaron&#39;s Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>amthompson012@gmail.com (Aaron Thompson)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>amthompson012@gmail.com (Aaron Thompson)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Camping on the lake</title>
      <link>/post/2021-10-15-camping-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>amthompson012@gmail.com (Aaron Thompson)</author>
      <guid>/post/2021-10-15-camping-trip/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The fire is the main comfort of camp, whether in summer or winter.&amp;rdquo; ~Henry David Thoreau
Camping is such an amazing time to disconnect, relax, and just hang out with those that you want to really spend time with. Because this past Monday and Tuesday was my Girlfriend&amp;rsquo;s fall break, we both decided that I would take some PTO for Monday, and we&amp;rsquo;d have a extended camping trip. Needless to say, it was well needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to, well, me!</title>
      <link>/post/2021-09-29-my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>amthompson012@gmail.com (Aaron Thompson)</author>
      <guid>/post/2021-09-29-my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hi all, and welcome to my website!
There are going to be a lot of things that are going to end up on this blog, but to begin with, I&amp;rsquo;m just happy you&amp;rsquo;re taking the time to read this!
First, a little bit about me! I am a Security analyst by day, and a lot of different hats by night. Wether I&amp;rsquo;m out camping, playing videogames, watching a movie with my girlfriend, or helping with church, I always end up being a bit busy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Resume</title>
      <link>/page/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>amthompson012@gmail.com (Aaron Thompson)</author>
      <guid>/page/resume/</guid>
      <description>Hi future employer (or nosey individual)! My name is Aaron, and I live in the Nashville Area. Although I am an information security major, I wear a multitude of other hats! Outside of work, I enjoy camping, cooking, playing videogames, or working with OpenSource software. In my home, I really enjoy putting work into deploying different servers, as it is both fun, and a easy way to ensure that I can better server you, my boss (or any other individual).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
